Guide to the Herbert C. (Herbert Coffin) Jones Papers, 1921-1944
Department of Special Collections
Herbert C. (Herbert Coffin) Jones Papers,
1921-1944
Special Collections M0208
Jones, Herbert C. (Herbert Coffin), b.1881?
6 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Gift of Mr. and Mrs. H. C. Jones, 1969.
Biographical Note
Lawyer and state legislator (1913-1934) from San Jose, California.
Scope and Content
Business correspondence, initiatives and referendums, legislation, scrapbooks, maps, newsclippings, and other papers, relating to Jones' career in the California State Senate and to State political activity after his term of office.
Container List
- Miscellaneous, including personal business correspondence, calling cards. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Building and Loan Associations. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence with constituents, job seekers, and complaints. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cooperatives. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Income Tax. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Initiative. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  See also Legislation-Direct.
- Initiative: Water. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Initiative and Referendum: Dept. of Education. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Initiative and Referendum: Measures. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Initiative and Referendum: Prize Fights. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Initiative and Referendum: Riparian Rights. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Initiative and Referendum: Weight Tax. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Initiative and Referendum: 1928. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Initiative and Referendum: 1930. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Initiative and Referendum: 1932. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Initiative and Referendum: 1936. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Initiative and Referendum: 1939. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Initiative and Referendum: 1940. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Initiative and Referendum: 1941. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Initiative and Referendum: 1942. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Initiative and Referendum: 1944. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Legal Cases. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Legal Directory. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Legal Reform. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Legion, The American. (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Legislation: Bills. (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Legislation: Correspondence. (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Legislation: Direct. (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Legislation: Financial. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Legislation: Guild System. (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Legislation: Modern Tendencies. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Legislative: General File. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  See also: Special Sessions; Speakership.
- Legislative: After Session 1923. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Legislative: 1928. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Legislative: Budget, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Legislative: Record. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Legislative: Suggestions. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Legislative: Suggestions, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Legislative: 1935. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Legislative: 1939. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Legislative: 1940. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Legislative: 1943. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Legislators. (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Legislature: Intrahouse Organization and Business. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Legislature: Procedure. (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Legislature: 1933. (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Legislature: 1934Special Session. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Power Trust. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Racing. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Racketeering. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Railroad. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Railroad Commission. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Regulations. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Relief Administration. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Relief Commission. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Religious Instruction. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Reports. (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Republican Party. (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Revenue Bonds. (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Riley Plan. (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Road Tax. (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Rolph (Governor of California). (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Salaries of Public Officials. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Sales Tax. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Santa Clara Valley Water Conservation District. (Box 5, Folder 3, Folder 4)
- Self-Governing Bar. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Senatorial Campaign of 1928. (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Senatorship. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Shortridge, Senator (Cal.) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Single Tax. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Soldier Legislation. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Special Sessions. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Special Session: 1928. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Speakership. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Stamp Tax. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Stephens Campaign. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Supreme Court (U.S.) - Primarily dealing with 1937enlargement plan of Franklin D. Roosevelt. (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Syndicalism. (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Taxation. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Taxation. (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Taxation: 1933. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Taxation: 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Telephone. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Tenure. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Text Books. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- 3% Contracts. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Trade Marks. (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Reemployment--Unemployment, Governor's Commission. (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Unemployment. (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Usury. (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Vice. (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Vivisection. (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Voting. (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Water and Power: 1924. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Water and Power: 1926. (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Water and Power: Reports and Clippings. (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Water and Power: 1931Legislative Committee. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Wright Act, 1926. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Young, Sanborn. (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Young, Sanborn: Dinner. (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Clippings, Newspaper. (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Maps. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Scrapbooks
- Newspaper clippings On topics in and action of California State Legislature, and the California political scene:
  - A) 1923: January - April 27.
  - B) 1923: January - May 18.
  - C) 1925: February 23 - April 24.
  - D) 1926: July - September.
  - E) 1931: January - April.
  - F) 1933: January.
  - G) 1933: January 1 -19.
- 2. Copies of Bills Introduced In the Legislature By Senator Jones, 1921.